realpoor.com 2009-11-30

# :: Ultimate MMORPG Gaming Community & Trading Zone

## RealPoor.com Privacy Policy

REALPOOR.COM is firmly committed to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website, including the RealPoor.com. 

Since the protection of your privacy is very important, we have adopted the following practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. Eventual changes to this Privacy Policy Act will be also available on this site. 

###  SECURITY AND LIABILITY 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. This site maintains a dedicated server with restricted access only to authorized user accounts. The webmaster, administrator and moderators cannot be held responsible if data integrity on the site becomes compromised. 

###  PRIVACY IN A PUBLIC 

Any information disclosed on the REALPOOR.COM Discussion Boards, or comments and replies in other sections (Articles, News, Videos) will be visible in public, in exception of "Elite Trading" section which hides all the information posted by the user, which means all the private data from Elite Trading will remain confidential. This means that all discussion board posts are visible through subject search engines and available to any reader worldwide. Therefore, we strongly suggest you not to post or offer your name, email address, home address, telephone number, or any other contact information if not willing to do so. Email addresses can attract spammers that are difficult to control. If you want to exchange your personal contact information with other members, please use REALPOOR.COM Private Messaging system. We also recommend that you do not register your real name, your unique email address, or the name of a website as a potential username. Keep your username anonymous. 

Information including, but not limited to, email addresses, mailing addresses, telephone numbers, names, websites or links, personal profile settings, signature, posts, surveys, polls, private messages, websites, and research studies will be removed without any prior notice. 

###  EMAIL NOTIFICATIONS & REALPOOR NEWSLETTER 

REALPOOR.COM does not send promotional or commercial emails to its users without permission or prior terms compliance. REALPOOR.COM may email its users periodically to inform them about the status of the website or of upcoming changes to the site, and for feedback on satisfaction questionnaires. Additionally, we inform users about changes to our privacy policy via email. Your email address may also be used to confirm your registration details and password (and for sending new passwords should you forget your current one). Further, REALPOOR.COM may email a user at any time regarding issues with his/her account. Confidential, private or semi-private information included in the content of emails received from or sent to you will not be disclosed to anyone at any time unless required by law. Registered REALPOOR.COM members may subscribe during registration process to receive Monthly REALPOOR.COM Newsletter, but also may unsubscribe anytime they want and remove their email address from subscribers list. REALPOOR.COM Newsletter contains monthly summary, including collection of information which contains news, articles, most visited and interesting discussions and trades, as well as other site related announcements & events. 

###  WHAT INFORMATION DO YOU GATHER AUTOMATICALLY FROM VISITORS? 

We use your IP address (the series of numbers associated with your individual computer) to help us maintain our site and identify problems with our server. Your IP address does not disclose any personally revealing information about you. 

We do use cookies to identify traffic that comes through advertising and to facilitate a more user friendly experience. Cookies are small pieces of information that a web site places on your computer's hard drive so we know it's you when you visit. This helps us to create a personalized experience for you when you visit our site. The use of cookies is a very common practice on the Internet. If you are uncomfortable with this, you can disable all cookies through your browser settings. Your enjoyment of our site won't be affected if you have set your browser to reject cookies. 

###  WHAT INFORMATION WILL YOU ASK ME FOR? 

When you register to use any REALPOOR.COM service you will be asked for some general identifying information which will enable us to provide you with this individualized service. We gather contact information (like your email address), demographic information (like your city of residence or age). We may share some of this information for our own research purposes with our professional advisors or consultants and third party partners. However the shared information will be limited to non-personally identifying demographic information shared under cover of a confidentiality agreement. We will only use this information in the course of providing our service to you. 

Once you have registered, you will be given the option of editing of your profile (personal description, password and contact information). 

REALPOOR.COM does not send promotional or commercial emails to its users without permission. REALPOOR.COM may email its users periodically to inform them about the status of the website or of upcoming changes to the site, and for feedback on satisfaction questionnaires. Additionally, we inform users about changes to our privacy policy via email 

###  HOW WILL THIS INFORMATION BE USED AND WHO HAS ACCESS TO IT? 

If you choose to have them sent to you, we may use your contact information to send you valuable updates and timely notices of promotions and mailbox status reports. Our site provides you with the opportunity to opt-in to receiving different types of communications from us at the point where we request registration information. You may modify this choice at any time by clicking on "UNSUBSCRIBE" button at the right side of NEWSLETTER box available at almost any page of the website. We reserve the right to use your contact information at any time to advise you of any updates that may materially affect your rights or status on our site. 

Your non-personally identifying demographic information is used to personalize your experience, allow other members to find you through a search, to compose your personal profile - which is associated with a pseudonymous identity you have created (username). Your contact information are available to other members only if you pre-set this options, otherwise our default setting will allow other users to see your contact information only, without demographic characteristics. Non-registered users (visitors) are not able to see your contact information or to contact you through Private Messaging system until they subscribe and become a valid REALPOOR.COM community member. In the event that you decide to buy one of our products or services, you will be asked for your financial information (like credit card number) which cannot be read by others when you initiate your order through a secured system. You will know you are in secure mode when the tiny padlock icon - located at the bottom of your browser - appears "locked". We are using CLICKBANK & PAYPAL for billing purposes. They pledge that the information you enter will not be shared with any outside party without your expressed consent (does not include fraud cases) and that any emails you receive from them will be related to your order. However, either CLICKBANK or PAYPAL are not the owner for this services, it's just a partner and billing processor. The personally identifiable information we collect from you is used for internet review and to improve the content and functionality of our web server or customize the layout of our pages for each individual member. The specific information we collect is not shared with other organizations and we will never release your personally identifiable information to an external organization without your prior consent except for the purposes of validating credit information and collecting debts. We may disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by operation of law, which may include, but is not limited to a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on REALPOOR.COM. 

Although REALPOOR.COM makes use of up to date technology in order to protect your pictures, audio and video recordings from being copied or captured by unauthorized third parties, please keep in mind that we cannot ensure complete protection. 

###  HOW LONG DO YOU KEEP THE INFORMATION I'VE GIVEN YOU? 

We keep the information you have given us for as long as you are a member on the site or for as long as we are required to do so by law, which ever is longer. 

###  CAN I CHANGE THE INFORMATION I HAVE ALREADY GIVEN YOU? 

You can always verify or request the removal of the personally identifiable information we have collected and change your registration information by selecting "Profile" from the main menu on the site. 

###  DO YOU MONITOR ONLINE BEHAVIOR? 

This is a community site where the members communicate to share the information using our forums. Also our members communicate with each other through instant private messages. We do not, as a rule, monitor members' private message exchanges, but we reserve the right to do so if user is using our service for the purpose of solicitation or any other violation of our Terms of Use or Privacy Act. Member submissions that appear on the public area of the site are moderated and, if necessary, we reserve the right to edit, delete, remove or not use any communication on a public area of the site. 

Members may choose to participate in community polls. The results of these polls do not reveal any personal identifiable information linked to the individual voters. 

###  WHAT SECURITY FEATURES DO YOU HAVE? 

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, our payment processors encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). SSL is the leading security protocol on the Internet. It ensures that information being transferred over the network is private through a process called encryption. Once encrypted the information is an unintelligible code until it is decoded upon arrival at the authorized destination. 

REALPOOR.COM follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

###  ADVERTISERS 

REALPOOR.COM uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

All information about Advertisements and Advertising on RealPoor.com is strictly defined in [Advertising Policy](http://www.realpoor.com/polices/advertising_policy.php). 

###  IMPORTANT NOTICE FOR TRADERS 

When using REALPOOR.COM for trade of virtual items, we strongly suggest not entering details that might compromise your game status. This is particularly concerning trading of game accounts, where members should not post account name in public, because it could lead to suspension or ban from the game. Instead, exchange your account names using REALPOOR.COM private messaging system or edit any picture that might reveal your account name or any other information related, before posting it in trading topic. 

###  MODIFICATION OF POLICY 

REALPOOR.COM may revise this policy without notice. If you continue to use our discussion boards after such changes have been made, you automatically accept those changes. 

**Last updated on October, 10th 2009.**
